To download the latest version of blender , search Blender in your browser
In the results, click on the first link, www.blender.org.  We can see the download button there.   You can click it to download the file.
I am using Windows OS, You can select the file according to your choice. Apart from windows there are files for mac and linux.
I have selected windows installer , and the files will start to download automatically when clicked.
I am fast forwarding the downloading process.
Now the file has been downloaded
You can double click and run the file.
Now a blender window will pop-up, you can tick the agreement and click next, specifying the install location.
When the installation is complete you can click the Finish button.
Then you can search blender in your search bar and open the program.
You can see this Interface when the program is open. These are the basic interface settings that you can tweak.
For example you can change the theme to deep grey or white.
Then you can press continue and choose general layout.
This is the opening layout for blender, you can see a default cube geometry.
And this is the installation procedure.
For those who want to approach blender professionally, I am planning for a set of tutorials in this channel
Interested can subscribe my channel, you can support me by liking my content if its good ,
and comment your opinion below which can guide me to prepare my next contents.
see you next
time